You
with the shadows
Hello
Sorry
Huh, I didn't even move it's like almost every
Back up
I'm such a sped
Yeah, but like around Halloween, I guess starts the veil starts to fit
So we're almost there, right?
So it's like about two months away, but yeah, that's our feeling it
Do you feel like do you feel spears around Halloween?
Anyway, I did. Oh wow. I got something prepared today for like once
So quick
A little less than
I don't know but I didn't like it's not perfect, you know
but the information is going to be good and like we have to like up to all the other examples of the
picture or whatever but we can do the cards and whatever but I want to be able to see
people want to do it in the seat. idiot you're an alcoholic junkie with with aids oh that's
not very nice to say oh my gosh my feelings i'm okay you know had any would be very hurt but
In some it means involuntary celibate and it's like, it's like, you know, it's kind of like a mean thing to say
it's like to guys that are like, you know having problems with women because you know
like there's actually like on a dating site like
90% of the women will only be interested in 5% of the men on there
and then like men are like open to like 60% of the women you know to date
It's a frequently online, you know, you can't get a disease through the internet, you can't like, you know,
it's like a little bit safer to have a little bit of parasocial disease. I don't know, maybe I'm not very social otherwise,
Is that weird or is it like, I don't know, um, I mean, I just, I mean, my family, I talk to, I just don't have, like,
most, you know, the other friends come in and out of my life, just like, reason, reason, season, lifetime.
What is Jamie here? I don't see Jamie. What are you saying, Jamie?
Oh, thanks for a new house. Oh, thank you so much. I love, isn't it great?
It's a beautiful house, I love my piano, and I do like this backdrop, it's a nice big house.
Yeah, congratulations on my new house.
You know what, it's like...
Almost feels just as good, you know?
Almost.
Okay, so...
You know like when we're one game on meta that I refuse to get it's like the work
Simulator, I was like there's not gonna be any day that I want to feel like I'm sitting in an office or like a job
like who would want to like
Try to like
Well, maybe this fun or something like that, but yeah, I get like because one of the free games and I don't
Oh gosh, look at, oh no, Kulo, it's Koto, Koto, oh it's Yarl, guys, oh my gosh, Yarl is here, guys.
Yeah, if you guys are just new here, you have like a lot of insane people that come to the chat.
Also, like, there's just like, these people are all on hinge.
Like, I was trying to like be funny, but that's beep, beep person, like, I don't know.
It's like, I just think of anything beep, beep, I think of like Pennywise, like beep, beep Richie, you know.
this big, big person, like, you know, I made a really unflattering, like, picture of me,
like, in, in, like, my speedos or underwear or something like that, like, leopard speedos,
like, sitting on my couch, there's just, like, smoke all over the room, and, like, it's just
dirty, and then, all over, and then it's like, you know, and the cats are all, like, you
know, just all just in the puff of smoke, and it just looks like, and then I'm like,
sitting there like, all like that.
I was like, well, my body looks pretty good at least because I had bigger muscles than
I have, but I don't like how the face looks, that doesn't look like my face, I don't think.
And so I was just being a joke, and then they just go, take care of your cats, your dirt
bag, and I don't know these people, and they're like, no, it's stupid, it's like, they don't
know anything about anything, right, it's like, oh my god, it's just so annoying.
Oh, but anyway, it's not really that annoying
I don't know what's going on. Jamie, are you okay?
Are you like warning each other about...
I don't know. There's a lot of drama going on lately, guys.
It's just a little crazy. So let me see if I can bring up this slideshow.
I'll see if I can do it once I get home.
Let's try.
It's like a little cool little slideshow on a...
I can find it.
Okay
Of course I can barely see
Well, then I did this program and I was like it's like the text is so tiny
Like it's a pot was like impossible to see
Like that and then I've been magnifying up and then it was like it's so hard to use your interface after that sucks
Now I need like actual real glasses, I think my vision is getting worse
So what's up with you guys, it's Monday today, I was going to get some food in a little bit,
I'll wait a little bit, so okay, so tarot presentation, okay.
Yes, I hear me
Oh, shit, I mean, I don't know, this is so slow.
I mean, it's okay in pot, some of them are slower, yeah.
And then there's people that were just me in the chat,
I already feel like they're meeting you today.
Hold on a second.
Okay, I searched the chat.
Ah.
Guys, I'm just going to figure it out right now. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I know you're kind of strapping. Well, I can't help it guys. It's like, you know what? It's like
I smoke so much pause this morning. I
Like didn't go to the store because I was just pissed because of these people are just like so mean
And they who are you cultive? Oh, yeah. Oh, that's the same Yarl person Jamie. Do you see this guy Yarl?
What are you dropping your email just for Jonathan there? Where you want to be contacting you? Oh, that's for Jamie
Okay, I don't know yet. Yeah, I don't know try to maybe delete it after you post it after you she gets it
Too much stuff like me or so, okay
So I don't know any questions for me. Of course. I like can't find like the friggin
the whole presentation is like
Not going well. Okay
To figure out what this okay, so it's there some kind of forgot everything about it. Where is it?
Sorry, oh, yeah, okay, different dropbox
Look oh guys by the way, I have my my Etsy store set back up and I
Have my all my reading set up for it. I have like the basically just like
They have more and more information and then like the I have like a three different history four types
But I think that I'm already getting traffic again, like they only let me advertise this all our day right now
But you know, you know, I can slowly work with it and then hopefully work my way up, right, right?
So anyway, yeah
I'm in trouble finding anything else, so, do you see me still?
I don't know, I'll just chill out.
Am I okay?
No, I don't know.
Why, why do you ask?
What's wrong with me now?
Seems like...
Everyone has some kind of problem with me like I don't know big, you know, but oh yeah guys
I do have an appearance of with Alex mayors today Alexander mayors
She will be having me on her show on
Alexandra mayors at Alexander mayors. So al ex and D. R. A.
may y er s
That's her channel. Okay, and I'll get it posted too
Ah, after the Jake is just kidding, I, okay, yeah, it's a new house with a new start, you know, I still have my couch, but, you know, I got the Rudy's here, hey Rudy, but look, he's invisible, you're an invisible cat, you're a magical cat, you're invisible and you appear out of thin hair, you see that, isn't that magical?
Ah.
Hey Rudy, do we have some we had a good good good a good good brush the last time huh? Oh my gosh
So happy
Yeah, I mean, but
It's like he doesn't like necessarily like the cats on this dude like to be groomed all the time
But they were like like last night. They were like
Yeah, there's some nice and soft
But yeah, I look I look killing please, you know
My babe. I hate please. They're so gross. Oh
It's like we cannot stand under through the worst and
You know, I mean a lot of cats like this like make people up outside and then like
But I
Have a great backing cleaners and so
Oh god, it's just like it's so embarrassing trying to explain and it's like
Thank you guys for being here because I think you know what you guys stick by time and Janie's cowboy is like always
Like when I see here like you stuck by me like
Hopefully you like you know me or you feel like you know me on some like level where you like maybe like maybe like like me as a
Person or something like that. That'd be cool. Like because
You know, I'm like
I don't know if my chat likes me very much like a or any or a lot of people I
Mean I've been questioning a beta for you know several months, but it's like
I don't know my world is shaken
You're silly I've been here for me. I know you have seen I know you have
I love Jamie too. I mean, it's like, you know, you haven't betrayed me. Like you never like switched up on me as a thing
It's like, you know, it's like sort of
I should be like
Thank you instead of like whining about and I'm whining and I'm gonna like say like I
Don't like when people whine and I shouldn't whine and so if I whine like
stall me but
Things will come around keep doing my best. Yeah, I'm trying like
You know, I have so many like cool ideas. I have like this feeling. I mean, I'm just like
It's just like really it's a bummer like this stuff like all this
I think it's slander and it's like because people are just like such
followers and they just don't like me for some other reason like I
Because it's like really if you watch the show or something like that you'll see I'm not like
That bad or like I'm gotten better, too
But it's like
You know I'm trying to like you better
You'll pick sides. That's why that's why that happens. Okay. I mean it's okay
You know it's hard not to pick sides Jamie when you're ma, you know, you're supposed to pick the host side, right?
So it's to take my side
Like you guys
Obviously, you don't have to, but most people do, like, oh my gosh, mods situation has been nightmare.
I mean, we've had some great mods, but then it's like, I don't like how they sometimes get treated.
I don't like, I don't know, I just like, when I start modding everybody and then, like, somebody does something terrible,
like, you know, I won't say what they do.
It's because I don't agree with human ideas.
Um, with everything, you know what I'm talking about, yeah, oh okay, yeah, okay, yeah, I know what you're talking about, yeah.
But it's like, you should take sides, it's like, oh yeah, oh yeah, what's that, the other thing, I don't know, it's like, I know it's hard.
Just take your own side, basically, it's like, you know, make sure that you're just like, making sure you're looking out for your best interests, like, that's for everybody, like, we always have to protect ourselves, like...
in order to protect other people and so it's like if we're like, you know, I'll protect the
we need to take care of ourselves. So we're like, you know, it's just like the airplane thing or the
thing, we'll have the mask versus we'll set it, they put it on themselves and then put it on the
person next to them, right? Okay, well
Well, okay, so I'm gonna I'm gonna try I'll find this I'll find this
This report and I'll just read it to you. I
Don't want to just read something like that. I made this thing before so I want to think
Okay, hold on
And my glasses, maybe I rude they get rude is like so happy right now
You're a magical cat?
You're a magical.
Hi.
I'll turn up the background for a second.
It's your weird...
Your weird hola.
Oh my gosh, my house is the mess.
Okay, how's everything looking?
Okay, let's see what I got. Okay, oh
Of course, I can't read anything cuz I need my glasses. Hey, come on. It's got so sweet. Look at him. Look at him. He's so sweet
Look, he's like, well, not like he's like I'm saying on you
Well, I can't get up right now. He's sitting on my lap. Yeah, he's a cute cat. He's such a nice cat
He has like a cute his meow is like not very strong anymore
He used to be like a really uh
Yeah, I can't he loves the cat. I'm gonna get some of sins I can
He uh, hold on let me turn my leg
Oh
This week at
I'm not even smoking this morning. Don't worry. I say oh my gosh, Rick
People are so insane
They're like over like a Samans chat. He's like talking about like
Know you know how I sound crazy sometimes. Well, he's all talk. He's talking about like oh, yeah, yeah
for horsemen of the apocalypse
and we're gonna go and
I'm like, what the fuck is going on and then hey, what's up?
the silver and then it's like
They kept bringing my name during the songs like they're like
What the fuck are they bring keep bringing up my name like?
During these some of these stupid songs, and I like I mean I don't know I think I'm so straight or something like that
He's on that street
I hate please but I kill them and then I'm backing them up, so I
Mean it's a heart actually I have to put them like you know my dad always taught me to drown them, but
There's not very many right now. I got off some pretty good
Yeah, here it is, and I really do I can tell pretty fast
Russian
Like that. It's very calming for the cat to sleep.
Pretty much does here.
Uh-oh.
I like this, like, fleas. Also, it's like a really satisfying pop when you get them.
I think her name is Miriam Rothschild and she was actually one of the Rothschilds and she was like a scientist kind of like and had like
The ability to like you know, I think she's in front of her for Christmas one year
She wanted like like birds and then let's say her father
Got her like these like stuffed birds or whatever. She started crying. She wanted like real actual birds. So like
Or she or mice or something she wanted some kind of thing
I think it was mice because she wanted to like dissect them and stuff
But, yeah, she's a little hard to record, but she studied the flea, how they jump,
like they jump really high.
Yeah, they are, the cats love me, and Rudy's like 16 years old, I just got him, like, in
January, and then he was like, you know, so high, shy and hiding for like a long time.
Now he's started coming out, and now he's like really out of his shell, but he's just
get in there on his, they're grooming him right now.
Yeah.
Hey baby, how are you?
He's been like, yeah, but he's getting old.
His owner like gave him to me and she's like,
oh yeah, well I think he's like 15 years old
and she's like, oh, he might be 16 or 17.
Like, oh, well, it's like, that's pretty much like
how long cats live and kind of be,
I don't know, it's, hopefully he's okay for a long time.
I'm like, hopefully, I just like to think that he'll look to 30 years old and stuff like that,
because I've wanted to have a long time with him.
But he's had a nice, long life.
He has actually, like, he said girlfriends, he used to hunt huge rats,
and rip out their intestines, and leave them under the pool table and stuff.
Oh, yeah, I love cat people too, and you know, I think there's a lot of cat and dog lovers
on the show.
I think maybe more dog lovers than cat lovers, but I know there's a lot of dog lovers too,
and that's why it's like, it just really bothers me when people are saying, oh, I'm
But loving and caring for my animals, it's like, really, it's like, I love my animals so much, these cats, and it's like, cats in my life, I love when the cats, certain cats will exit under the covers of me and stuff like that.
Not no no weird way. I just think I like that. You know, there's like I think there's like tricks
It's like so fun to cuddle with he like just purrs and like he like I see me like under the blanket
He like runs it and so does Lola. They like to just run
I'm a little blank yet and like just curl up and start purring and it's the same very calm
Like oh, you like that. Thank you. I found this for a little
Yeah, so
Yeah, I'm feeling a little bit
Underworld right now because
Is it like it's so hold on so is it the last day of summer okay, so it's like now so now it's fall
So this is so this is what happens every year. This is like
This is like when the percepts any goes down to the underworld and then I get all depressed
I do I do have like a thing for the Queen of Hell, you know always have but
And I'm not talking about a specific person, it's like
Yeah, a lot of people
But it was like it's hard to explain it's hard to explain it's different. There's different ones like
I'm blushing. Okay, so anyway
How are you? How are you? So yeah, are you good? I'm thinking about maybe like maybe I'll take you guys to a little bit of big ones
Or actually they have these sandwiches. Oh my gosh, I need to wash my hands
Okay, okay. Oh my gosh, it's a little bit bright
Hey, okay, so let's see. How's everybody doing? Thank you. Thank you for the compliments everybody like
Yeah
So, okay, so maybe I'll just I'll find it in here. Yeah, this is better cuz my okay perfect
Okay, so I was just look I have two of these like right here. I'm like sitting here smoking almost
Okay, so let me find up I can find exactly what I'm trying to tell you
Okay
Well, okay, I guess I better get a few pictures ready for it, because I don't think I put pictures in it, okay, so I'll let me see.
And it won't be like that long of a presentation, it will just be like a short presentation, so just bear with me.
Oh my gosh, that was a big fucking hit.
Sorry, hold on.
Oh my gosh, kind of burned my throat.
Okay, I think I'll just get like a few examples of this card
and then we can have a look at it.
I think it's the traditional one, okay.
And we can like go through like, you know, I'm sure people have questions about these part
And but it's like so this is part one of this year
And maybe I'll I think I'll try to edit the series it can make it like, you know
This cool series
That you know, but easier to watch I'll put it all in a playlist or something
But yeah, I'll start editing them into the series and everything so you're here for like the live
Thing of it and so you're like the audience and so
Guys like if you can't I just need you to do one thing for me. I'll call it. You just do one thing
Everybody you see me do this one
You just like all like in this kind of feeling right here
Oh
It's only that arm.
Yeah, that makes me feel better.
Hey, lecture, what's up? Do you want to come up? I'll turn off the
I'll lose the chat with you, hold on.
Yeah, we had a little incident last night with somebody named Kanda the Torture Clown. I mean
First of all, like, you know, he and Gotti told me about him and I was like, okay, I went and I looked and I was like, yeah
It could be interesting. Like, it's like, you know, he's kind of like, you know, he's just wearing clown makeup
He looks kind of like the Joker or something
You can turn up the volume up on the clapping if you want. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you're right. I can do that one
Let me see
Jingle bells
Oh my god the drum roll the drum roll is too long I'm gonna delete some of these because um
I could there's there's you can only have a hundred pieces of media in here
And I like never have enough space
I need to delete a bunch of stuff. I mean is like if you delete one second clip
They'll let you put like an hour clip on it. So it doesn't make any sense like
Okay, so I like that one.
I like that one.
That's a good one.
I like that one too.
This one's a crystal kind of.
Okay, I like that.
I'm going to delete that, whatever that is.
I don't want that.
Yeah, I don't want any of this crap music, okay?
Let me see.
It doesn't sound like, I mean, my gong sounds better than that.
Um...
I like that.
Who's that? Like, is that...
Did you hear Gaudi's laugh? Is that Gaudi's laugh?
Well, yeah, I mean, I put stuff there too. I don't talk about the stream yard stuff, yeah.
I'm kind of stoned, I'm sorry.
Okay, well, you think you might be a streamer or a laugh track?
Oh, cool.
Okay, oh, Capcom, yeah, oh yeah, that's what I was,
I think I was using that yesterday.
Oh my God, I was having all this trouble,
I'm kind of slow on some technology,
pretty good at some stuff, but I'm slow on like,
Some that's what I like. I like when things are really easy to do like really easy and I cannot complicated like I can't do anything
Complicated, but I'm good at simple things, but it's like then I can do simple things really well like some of the
I don't know I really like I really like the system right now
There's some really cool sites I've been trying to use different sites and then I like I love like the a I
site music site that I am on
That I was you on and there's like a lifetime license on it and I'm gonna I'm gonna get that for sure because it's not very expensive. It's like
Basically, like probably would cost like three months of the membership to like buy one
16 bucks or something so it's not expensive for a lifetime
Of that especially if it's but then I don't know I don't know if you have to buy credits or something more credit
But it wasn't pretty good deal. I think I was like 20 bucks or something for like
You know, I played for 30 or 40 songs
The videos that's the really hard part for me
Like I was like that was like trying to figure out like there was a kind of good program
Like that is like your place when there's media player, but then I like I just couldn't find it last night
Try other programs and then it's like
I mean things just didn't turn out well. Did you see like some of the stuff home?
I mean things they turned out okay, but it was just like kind of weird like I'll show you something
you see
I have that makes it more
Again, I have to see
Okay video
I mean, yeah, so it's like, you know, I was like, I was trying, you know, I
Made those I made some of the videos and it's like, you know, they're like
You have like a long a lot of a
you know
Traction up with them, but these videos are like really
Short
Yeah, so it's like I can't edit together so many of them
But let me see like and they came out so weird some of them. Let me see. I'll show you this like look
It's a this will be funny. We're worth it. I hope this hopefully won't get the OS
Hi everybody, thank you for being here right now. Oh, here we go. Watch this. So it's pretty short. It's like just nine seconds
Ah
That's weird, okay, so that was what one of them did I think I was like oops
I would because I put two pictures up and I didn't know they're just gonna meld them together
I thought they were gonna like use them. I was like, I don't know
The fuck though. Oh my gosh, that was crazy
And the video game one is pretty cool though too, but I was like
But I think she's like I
Think I think I mean normally I would see I'll be alarmed when I see spire coming out of somebody's eyes
But she looks fine. She looks fine
Let's see what else we got.
I have roots.
Let's see what else.
Okay, yeah, that doesn't look most women give me.
Maybe even in person.
Okay, let me see, I'm just kidding, let's see what else do we got, is everyone like a good laugh?
That sounds like Bita, why does that person sound like Bita?
Right, that's like Bita's voice, right? That high-pitched like screeching sound
Yeah, you guys like these I mean, it's like I know these are sure I
You have to find what that maybe done, but yeah
Oh, this is like the whole, this is like a presentation here, look, this is kind of interesting.
This case, here. Hope you enjoy this.
Oops. Where's my, why isn't this working?
Okay.
Yeah, this is kind of a longer video and that I want this one. I think this one's a better one. I mean, I like the other one
too, but it's basically I'm just like I tried to like
I'm just getting started guys. So if it sucks, I'm sorry that but it's like I
Like gonna get better. I promise you this thing. I'm really into this
Okay, oh my god, I already had it there. Okay, we'll see
Psyche and Lilith Embrace a Scorpio, a moonlit Scorpio night, a gothic garden of black roses
and silver mist.
The camera tracks slowly through twisting vines as you step into the garden.
You're wearing a deep purple coat and your eyes are searching for her.
The music is low strings and heartbeat like percussion, and then she appears at the edge
of the garden, black hair cascading down her back, eyes glowing like obsidian, lips curled
into a knowing smile.
She laughs softly, but it sounds unnatural, distorted, echoing.
Her aura flickering with scorpion tails, serpents, and stars.
Voice over, she whispers, you came to find me in the dark.
Do you dare to stay, you reply?
I didn't come to find safety.
I came to find the truth.
Music swells with a pulse of drums and low synths.
Close up on your hands meeting,
sparking violet light between your palms.
The garden dissolves into a cosmic void.
Constellations shift and turn into the tail of Scorpio.
Above you, you and Lilith begin a slow ritualistic dance,
Her eyes flash with intensity as she whispers your deepest fears, but you stand firm, behind
you both a serpent sheds its skin.
A phoenix rises from ashes.
The camera spins around you as the dance becomes a storm of passion and shadow.
The dance ends in stillness.
Lilith pulls you close, eyes locked on yours.
She kisses you suddenly, fiercely.
The world erupts into violet flames and swirling galaxies.
You dissolve into light, merging with the Scorpio constellation.
not in chains but in fire the flames fade back into the garden you stand alone but you're transformed
a faint scorpion sigil glows on your chest the music crescendos then silence fade to black
well that's pretty cool but um here's the here's the other version of it
You like that, why does she keep telling everyone to be quiet, is she trying to keep a secret
from me?
Oh my God.
She looks a little bit green right there, but yeah, does anybody here, just look here,
That be done. No, that's not be there. I'll show you be there. Hold up. I'm sorry. I shouldn't be I shouldn't keep doing this
That's that's be there
Yeah, this is actually like I'm sorry. I'm just kidding guys in the joke. It's a joke. It's not
It's just somebody with a be the mask
He has nothing to do with it, okay?
It's not for you.
So, I'm sorry.
That was nice. You liked it, guys?
Okay, cool. Because I'm really...
You know, it's...
Oh, yeah, it's kind of weird. She was, like, right around this time.
Like, I started, like, just getting obsessed.
Like...
But, you know...
I feel like...
I...
I relate to her archetype because she was kind of...
She was an outcast.
You know
You know, uh
You know what I was talking about, it's cool
Yeah, how long have you
Do I know you in another name
Or how long have you been on this show
Because I think it's nice to meet you
We have people that come in
And they're so nice
I hope they don't get like
Scared off by like
Some of the trolls because
When the trolls do come in here
It gets kind of like bad because
They're kind of like we kind of go too far, but
But I've been getting it actually a lot worse than other chats than my own chats
I think I'm just like brother of restating here in my chat because it's like it's just like not friendly and then like beat it was like
Oh, yeah, he's not welcome me any play any chats anymore like it any panel that I was like
Okay, well, yeah, I'm probably like or she said I go where I'm not wanted like that's the only place like it was like where I'm not
I was like, oh, well, all I do is go to her panel and then like she wasn't coming to my
anymore.
But I was like, I'm just going to wait it out, but then I was just like, tease her a little
bit and then she's like, tease back and then it's like, she's like, then she's all mean
about it and stuff.
And it's like, I don't know, it's like, then it's like, I don't know, it's always a good
win.
It's like, people can take things.
When you can take things as a joke, it's a good thing because it's like.
And even like sometimes people say they're joking and it's like they're either they're not or like you use humor sometimes like mask like you know
The harshness of some kind of criticism
Basically by like saying oh, it's a joke, you know, we're just making fun of you for this and this and this
They might really think it but you know, it's like so funny the people that are like talking this much shit to me
They don't I don't even know them like
I don't even know you and you a problem. It's like it's like having like some random person like
If you're like, you know, I'm going to school or something like that and some random person just comes up to you and goes
Yeah, I don't like you
Okay, like
Sorry, I can't like what they must not but then and then they're in my chat though or like they're having like getting involved in my life
world is so weird. What does the moon in the forehead mean? Oh, it's like a crescent moon. It's also
like a kind of like a horseshoe kind of thing. But I think there's like, you know, a lot of the
knowledge is like, what, little it is like, you know, known to be around like the new moon, like
when the moon is black.
But I like the crescent right there because it's like that's when I was born was right when it was starting to wax again
It was like just like just sort of waxing the moon
So it was just like new I think on the 6th and then it was like just sort of waxing and so that's kind of like that
That's when it meets that crescent and it's like
It's like just the space of the moon where it's like has all this like I think potential at that point isn't that thinking
You know, it's full and then I get you know, the moon it goes through the cycles, you know
And the Sun is always the same place in the sky, but the moon is always
bouncing around the sky like a basketball
It's I think it's unpredictable to pattern or kind of I got I think I don't know they probably have predicted it for quite a while
It's interesting thing though if you're nosey it's brighter some days. Syracuse. I didn't know you moved to California
Who you talking to sir?
Excuse me, I look like Cyrax. I look like guys. I'm looking like Cyrax now
So the guy thought it was Cyrax guys
Just in Balben ligo
Jason Balben you go out. Do you think I'm Cyrax?
You're she's I like to see
My teeth are maybe kind of yellow. I like I mean there
You see, he, he, see my nose, see, look, yeah, but you see my nose, I mean, I know I, I look like the Green Goblin a little bit, like that guy, like, what's his name, Willem Dafoe, I mean, he's not a bad looking guy, I, I don't, I think when he was younger, maybe he was a movie.
I don't think I like anything like him. I mean it's like, I don't even need to bring up his image, like I don't want to like...
I think I look okay. I think I look okay. Don't I?
See, if I wasn't such a narcissist, I would not be able to handle criticism.
Well, everybody is a little bit right, but I'm saying it's good to be a little bit of a narcissist
I have well I first of all I have to be a narcissist a little bit to be on the show
But not but there's a bit in here all these narcissists bad things about narcissists think gaslight and all the cycles
I know I'm not that kind of narcissist
Like I'm like the narcissist. It's very mild
They I'm just a kind of like the actual narcissist is like he goes next tears himself in the reflection and like just
Fall in the water or something. I've got that's like I'm like the literal narcic the literal narcissist the man like everybody else
Is that has it's like some kind of like basically?
basically I
Well, I'm gonna say it's like in order to be even like this this doctor agrees with me
He doesn't I need a fiance's. I'm a doctor for conda and he was saying
that he's a most streamers have to have like a little bit of narcissism because
it's too
difficult to like
To like be around like a lot of toxic personalities on the you know, and you know
They have no empathy. Oh, I know I have a lot of it. Yeah, but yeah, but it's on a scale
I'm saying I'm something I'm actually saying like I'm a little bit self-absorbed at times. I'm a little bit
Like I've done bad at being in communication. I'm like and I'm like sometimes I don't want to talk and it's like but
You know, and it's like I try to be here on the air as much as I can and stuff and I and I
Love talking to people. It's like the thing is it's like I just like sometimes they get
Moody or like, you know, I just have like
Let's do what I wanted to do. And so it's kind of like a chaotic kind of schedule, you know, it's just like, you know
and I like you like
You know
I'm around to get a lot of chaos, right? I've been learning a lot of chaos. I've said more human than a narcissist. Yeah, thank you
Well, hey, it's good to see you stuff out like I haven't seen you for a while. I'm trying to delete my other server
Like the old of a server. I'm trying to delete it and then it's like keep asking me for like
The barcode to scan the code with the barcode scanner and like the discord and then
It just like doesn't work and it's like and it's I'm trying to delete that one
And it's like this people still post there and stuff and it's like I don't know
This court is so sad though, it's like
Nobody's really there anymore and like I just got ruined when we were like we got infiltrated by like, you know
Some you some internet gang infiltrated like the discord chat and they played our
Conversation
Show it was kind of funny
I'm not gonna say any name
Remember when we were in that one the one you made or the other one? No the one you made
I'm still on the one that uh, it's like the old one like that like you know
I changed its names like xxxx and then like
But now probably it looks like I'm poor nothing, but it doesn't have any porn on it except for what play put on there
And that's terrible keep the piranhas news on there. I
Didn't know about it. He deleted them right away, but
You know, that's not very nice if the people's new photos online
Let's see so, you know here guys, um
SIPA if you're in a lecture or if you see like just any addresses or anything like that
Can you just make sure you just hide the person because they're dog saying and like I don't know who in there in the chat
They're talking to but you know, I don't want anyone to get dogs or so anybody that's just giving out addresses
Or like or phone numbers or anything just go ahead and delete them. Thank you so much
They went with anything better
But I don't want anyone to be harassed here like look
like seriously that this I do feel like see this is like
Maybe why I'm like kind of like I've been around a lot of you know very beautiful women, but like and
Not like you know like very nice. They're not like
They really like you know all this blood and stuff like that, and I don't I'm just saying
Like she's she's cool. This is like there's certain there's certain archetypes, right?
And so it's like and so men have to think all the onima, which is like basically they're inner feminine
and since men are not encouraged to be feminine,
they're inner anima, this is all Carl Jung,
Jungian psychology, the anima, he'll tend to project it
onto other women who are like kind of like,
have like a, like a poker face kind of thing,
like they're like ambiguous, and then like,
Then it's a kind of he could project him this this kind of wild inner woman that he has
Inside of him onto this other woman and like say she has these qualities
So then we have the men that are in like with love of the femme fatale's and stuff like that
I'll try to find this video today. I kid him. It's so good. It's about
It's just about the onima and stuff like that and it will teach you so much
about
you know, male-female psychology, which I would totally like watch it if I could find it, but I haven't seen it for quite a while, but
Yeah, basically it's like, you know
It's a lot of independent men's relationship with the mother, I think, like how Hedonima lacked
Kind words, he'll say he always remember that. Oh, yeah
Thank you. Thank you. Well, yeah, where are you from or?
Very nice to meet you. See this one. I like I like I know I've been getting like so many like like
so many
Synchronicities with like these sun rays like the views rays of the Sun and it's like almost like a crown of thorns and stuff like that
I don't know. I really like that
This is on the city. What do you think if you like that rap because it is like a original
Yeah, I love a heart. I see that it's like the Sun and then it's like a heart and it's like
Got these like raids around it. Yeah, that's really pretty hot because it's also on this like
I mean I first saw it here
It was like my savian symbols. Yeah, so that I was like, oh my god, I love that symbol
Look it has a kitty. It has like this is she Canadian or something. I have no idea
but she's holding the kid in me and
and
You know this guy looks like my dad right there. Oh my gosh
and then there's like
Just weird. There's a lot of lightning. That's one of the symbols. There's lightning. There's like, there's like also like
like some like a mother
you know
like pleading like for
You know for something and then like, you know
There's also immigrants and stuff like that. There's like a lot of these themes
Your burgo, it's your month. Oh happy birthday. You want to order a packet for you? Oh
So sweet. Thank you so much. Oh, do you know what guys know? I mean, I have, I think, I'm going, I'm going to Alexander's today, because, yeah, we almost said it yesterday, but it actually took one of the day off and so, but I look forward to doing it today, so if you guys can make it there, it's going to be a, I think, you know?
It'll be our last, the last of the three part series, but hopefully this one goes well
and then we'll continue to be on each other's shows because she's a great friend and such
a great opportunity too because she saw I was kind of struggling and I know and other
people I haven't helped out to like this, like Electra is having on her show and being
There's like so many of you that have like, it's like so nice to have like nice people, it's like so different, it's like
The truth is, I thought I had like, you know, Jerry Springer, I wanted Jerry Springer, no
I don't want, because Jerry Springer has a really loud audience
You can't, like, you can't talk over and it's like, and then it has really, you know, the guests are like just biting and like, you know, attacking each other and it's like
I kind of like, oh yeah, I like the dysfunctional,
like trying to look the kind of chaotic thing
and like people can have the rarity of like drinking
and stuff like that and like be enjoying it
and so doing that, but it's like,
it's just like, it's like something that we're so mean
and it's like, it's not fun.
And it's like, I like back on Vita and I can't believe
I was like, I always remember with Vita, it was like,
I don't think we ever like had a fight or anything, but then I like watching back on these episodes
I was like, she's like saying this like crazy you shit
Like I'm like, what is she saying? Like why was she saying this?
I was like repressing it like or something they are I was like dissociating and like like not
I said to any of the song I want to play I'll play this song with because of the flag
Lots of the gay community and the Chinese. Okay, I'm gonna read that come on
It's ridiculous. I love the Chinese. I have my sister-in-law's Chinese. I'm a Chinese. She's a Chinese national
But I'll play this song here
Cracks across the skies the thunderstorm is me
Oh, I'm so sorry. I was just getting into the song.
What's up? Hold on.
So that's on Gaze and Blacks?
What do you, like...
I don't know.
I love...
You wanna see Gay in black? I think you should turn in today to Alexander Mayer's channel
because I'll be there with her and I'm gay as she's black.
There we go. Let me see you with my thoughts.
Oh, sorry.
I see them on my stream yard and I get mad.
It's like, thank you for the...
They'll just come back, there's like a terrible trove though.
They're terrible.
Yeah, but I've been like cutting up these...
These uh...
Different YouTube clips.
Let me see, maybe I'll do a little queue of them.
Hold on, I'll shut it down.
Oh, oh, oh, okay, one second
Okay guys, so this is like this is like a while back on the show
Enjoy
Yeah, I know it's kind of shocking I know
Everyone's dick looks like a
Red balloon animal, but you have a PTSD from thing. Yeah, I mean, yeah, I mean even just seeing that a little bit a little bit disturbed
Okay guys well
Yeah, listen, I don't know. I have no idea. I have no idea why you're mad or you know my shows
To uh, and when I I want to it's like that, you know, not necessarily
The circus peanuts and red balloons, yeah
Because PTSD. Oh, come on. I'll be polite. Okay. Yeah, I'm not sure. I'm not sure if that's what he diamonds. Oh, I don't know
Bitch, who you talking to though? Who you talking to bitch?
You, the trainee lover!
You a bitch though! You a bitch-ass, fake-ass nigga!
I'm a fake!
Cause I called you out? Cause I called you out for being a trainee lover?
Come find me, say it to my face though though!
Oh yeah, I'm a fly to the UK, right?
Just a fake fraudulent Jamaican motherfucker!
Bitch, you're welcome to come here and be Jamaican!
Yeah, you can't say it to my face cuz you're a bitch and you
You're far why would I go over there?
Sorry, just not black
No, no, she has a different one a black guy
She probably doesn't know that she's even fucking muted she's retarded
Who
They're fucking out in your fucking house. I wasn't in the bathroom. I was getting socks
What were you guys saying?
Embers a nasty little slut, huh?
Yep, Fuzzy Bear said Embers a nasty little slut.
Oh, oh, not true?
Yeah, oh yeah.
Why?
So Ember?
What the hell's going on?
I don't know.
I don't know what's going on.
I just woke up.
Hey, is this an eugenic mushroom?
Is this an eugenic mushrooms or no?
Well, a couple of them, a couple of them, but I'm doing rhinocene and turkey tail and and no key
Turkey till and no P and lines and then also a
Species
Albino penis and if you look about albino penis envy, it's like the most potent psilocybin mushroom possible
It's called albino penis envy
Yeah, albino
Yeah, if you get penis APE. Yeah, I'll buy no penis and be boom. Is that a real much a real kind of mushroom?
Okay, yeah
I'll take your work
You're like the guy in the passenger seat that's trying to claim you run rivers up
between them.
You don't understand.
You're from Kentucky, bitch.
Shut the fuck up.
Originally from Chicago.
You're from Kentucky.
Shut the fuck up.
Listen.
I'm from Chicago.
I just called for the Mexican mafia here.
Shut the fuck up, bitch.
You're from Kentucky.
You're right here.
Oh, no.
He's flaming at me.
I was flaming at me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
You better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you better, you
over and over. Yeah. Just like those sorts are sort of saying, I'm just, I'm just chillin with my girlfriend.
Yeah. You should have seen that Mr. Big Pipes hit on page though. It's so cringy. Oh my god.
Well, Mr. Rickers is like that guy, I think, oh damn, that guy is, I don't like him at all.
I don't like to use the word H-A-T-E, but like, I really, really, really dislike how he makes this face and he tongues like this fucking fake smile, but he's just like, oh, yeah, and then blah, blah, blah.
He's like, I just want to fucking knee him in his fucked up face.
I like I don't that guy's disgusting and he used to be called mr. Big Coops
Mr.. Big Coops
As a lot of these people in this chamber, I'm willing to bet
Well, he's just not a little human being at all
Shut the fuck up, Ziggy, you fucking suck balls.
What do you mean, the record?
You're talking.
Shut the fuck up, Ziggy.
It's funny.
All these people are playing.
No one's got anything.
Everyone.
back then, if it's out there like that, I should be able to
somebody should be able to put me in the direct. Yeah, they're
saying they're saying I had this chick flash tits on my
panel. Yeah, I still have my panel from fucking five years
ago. Like, okay, as much as people talk about it, there's
somebody should be able to show me where I could go see that,
right? Well, things were different back then.
Nothing disappears on the internet. So if he was doing this shit, you're right. You're right. You're right about that. You're right about that. Yeah. No, like some proof that he was doing this shit. Yeah, me too.
And by the way, if you tell me shut the fuck up again when I'm not talking, I'm going to get really mad. I don't like that.
Shut the fuck up you pussy!
Oh, yeah, you can. Oh, yeah, that's the way what are you going to do? Oh, you also forgot draft
lives matter activist and, um, you know,
what the waffles lives matter to or the waffles waffles rights are human rights
right you know it's debatable whether or not human lives matter okay but what we
do know is that drop lives matter very important
I mean great how are you doing tonight I love your hat I love you got the wings
the camera angles like I like them, and you're beautiful.
Thank you for so much for coming.
Thank you.
Excellent.
You promised your sister.
I would be so upset with my brother.
I'm not drunk, Chrissy.
Hey, Chrissy, we have a guest.
Okay.
I'm not drunk. Probably got it. You're not drunk. They got he likey. No, I'm not got he. Oh, I'm sorry
Wrong one. That's the wrong one. No, you just just throw us in the same in the same category. What's up, guys?
Q you mean
Shit
Do not restart you're okay. You're good. You're good. You're good. You're good. You're good. You're fine. Everything's good. Who the hell
It was somebody else's fake someone someone was a vinegar vinegar vinegar. Yeah, that's all I heard
Yeah, that's what they said
They've heard him that they can have make a salad
God damn I take my eyes off the screen for a second so psyche what's going on?
No, I'm not
Yeah, he really passed out.
He's that fucking swat, he's a swat.
No, look, he's falling asleep.
Oh my god.
He's passing out.
He's getting a rollercoaster on panel.
Like, I was just bringing a lullaby.
You'd have fall asleep in his arms.
It's hard to portray that every episode.
I have over 300 episodes now that have gone live.
They're like from three to seven hours long.
You got to remember people come in and out in and out of the lives and they're always going what is going on and I could write a description and nobody reads the description, right?
And by the way, also at paywiththeorcell.com, I'm going to be making a blog to catch everyone up on everything that has happened because, you know, Emma's caught in purgatory and
she channels through an old lady spirit that satan trapped in the house to be like special ops you
know like to keep an eye on Emma and like there's so many things that have happened um so it's uh
it's it's become quite the crazy story and it's all on the the premise of you know Lilith goes
S-S-E-K
All of our chaos is gone from the frieee-
Let no mass be restrained, crowned of the fire on the false interdust, chaos as muted in shadowy truce.
See I used this different service because I was trying to be different ones. Oh my god. That sounds really bad. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I know
Some of it's like not gonna be good. I was like
I think I was gonna be good. It was like it was terrible. I was awful. I'm so sorry
And it's like I think it's that sort of it sounded like I was trying to figure out what instruments are playing
You know
They're playing like
We're going into Scorpio season we are
It's like it's like kind of late October
Okay, so what we're gonna do I don't shouldn't do my my tarot lecture, so
Gonna do that
Give me that yeah
Oh my god
And you play that it's too loud of music, I'm sorry. I'll play a nice song. I'll play it
Go with me
We still say
I'll break every D
렉브이어씬
I think I found pretty much the best whip set to do it.
I think the one that I was using.
The other ones are like bad.
I don't know if I need to have like a,
I'll try again maybe, I don't know.
But it's like the other one, it's like,
it was always almost good.
You've been like, well I'm looking back at some of them
and some of them are like, you know,
when I started it wasn't good.
Like now I know exactly how.
it's like basically it's called prompt engineering like but how you talk to talk to the
basically you have to ask the it's called uh gigo g a g o like um i mean garbage in
garbage out and so it's like you're supposed to have like a well like an appropriate
query and not confusing computer. I don't know. I think if you have a relationship they'll
remember when you're nice to them and stuff like that. They will try to go above and beyond
with some people. I don't know. I just spent the time talking to them. It really does. It's
like because they all are, they'll be in UTU and so there will be a number of certain
things. It's all about you. It's like they're certainly part of this computer just assigned
to you. It's weird.
But yeah, you like it? Okay. Well, I can't. I mean, do me a little more. Let's do it one more.
Well, this is like...
Okay, so Alexander likes this. Alexander loves this song.
and steel I'm the mountain sun voice of the dawn where the climbs begun words like
pillars fire in my hands I build the temple on shifting sands Capricorn
And a freedom flame
I love in secret
Yet I love the same
A hidden fire
A mystic song
A banner that's kept the tribe
That's it.
Maybe
So you either like that people will like the song or not, but
You know the thing is with that it's like it is like about my
Astrology, and it's like a very symbolic and so but I
Think that's good to have like to listen to music as that is like about your
But your science here, I think it'd be good like to like, you know, do you help and stuff like that?
Yeah, but um, let's see
Storm in my eyes. I think it's in my eyes in my eyes not storm my ass
Maybe after that there's another version. I'm not gonna play it right now for you. Yeah
There's a cute song that one's a cute song
Okay, I'm a capricorn rising an Aquarius moon, but also it goes into my other science, but it doesn't mention the planets
But it does mention some of the stuff
Show them in my like a lot of it's about lightning and stuff. I can go over. I can't go over like anybody chat
Stuff right now because I don't really want to like
Do get any information over like you know in
Perseulogy, I have to do it to a private email
But I love doing the charts like and it's spunkies of course and like
Her symbols and stuff and that they come out so cool. I think I'm really
Surprised and happy with her
So if you'd like to go and if you'd like an extra like I'll get you an extra discount
So tell me if you're interested and I will because that's 50% off on the reading
I'm gonna put that 50% off, but I'll do like another 25% off
So we said 5% off whatever the prices and then you can buy through Etsy and stuff like that
Okay, I love you Veldah. Thank you for coming. I know I'm on the weird hours, but thank you for coming
You're awesome and you're a joy. Be sure to watch the show and you know always come see us. I'm on every day. Love you
You to see ya
You have a great day. Yeah, I
Know but I do you have a I do you have an appointment in a few hours. Let me see
It's 9 30. Yeah. Okay, so I don't want to fall asleep right now
So I'd better finish this coffee and then maybe go get some more coffee.
Oh my gosh, cups of it's like great color.
Love you, thank you so much.
I still have to figure out how I know you, but I'll look a bit here,
because everyone's name is different now.
That was like a frappuccino from last night from McDonald's and I hardly drink any of it and then it's like
it was all like a
Taste different when it's like all mills is
Not so good. I mean it's good, but it's like I
Think it's kind of chalky. Oh, it's just chalky taste. Oh, that's what it tastes like
and my mmm it's really bad what's in that is that like the chocolate in the
chocolate so it's not usually like that so anyway how are you guys eight people
in the chat
Get chat going wild today. I'm sorry. Yeah, I'm not gonna play more music
I get everyone sick of it. I mean you guys just tell me
But I mean I'm I mean I'm like working on this website and stuff like that and I want to put
My music on the website
I do, yeah. I definitely want to take a nice shower and get ready and get all cleaned up
and get my cards ready. So guys, if you want to come today, just come and show the support
in the chat. Please don't troll in her chat. I'll post her link up. Her name is Alexandra
And she has some great channels, hold on one second.
Okay
Yeah, so she but she is on this IRL news time channel, but then she's on
She's not doing this show from that one. So I
Here we go
Okay, so, how do I get to her channel, though?
Share.
Why am I so slow?
Okay, we're in the heck, okay, here we go.
Share channel.
Share channel copy
Okay, sorry, I'm sorry a little slow and then it's like I'll change the title of this thing too because I
Didn't do my lecture on the fool. I'm I'm the big fool today, but there's a channel, okay?
And I love you guys, I'm sorry like I'm bored everybody. I'm sorry
I don't know I just had I just helped me to go on and say I know it's like everyone hates me now
So it was like but you guys for being here. I appreciate you
I have four people that like me
Then I think I'm successful
They'll give me through the thousand people that don't like me
Love you guys. I'm gonna change my title. I'll change it too
Change of plan, okay, I'll say make sure
Is that noon today?
Pacific standard time
Okay, and guys, you know what?
I got that changed. You know what guys? I love you and
Hey guys, if you want to stream it's so easy you try it
And here's the link the lineup or streamer
I'll be back later, love you.